<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Tild</title>
    <link href="https://wagam.github.io/tild/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://wagam.github.io/tild" />
    <updated>2020-03-25T15:35:34+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Marc</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://wagam.github.io/tild</id>

    <entry>
        <title>TID 25-03-2020: A youtube channel : Design Course</title>
        <author>
            <name>Marc</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://wagam.github.io/tild/tid-25-03-2020-a-youtube-channel-design-course.html"/>
        <id>https://wagam.github.io/tild/tid-25-03-2020-a-youtube-channel-design-course.html</id>

        <updated>2020-03-25T14:31:57+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    A youtube channel : Design Course It is a very good youtube channel with amazing content. Every video is clear and concise. I like how everything is displayed and explained. I started to watch a lot of its video today and I want to reproduce almost all&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>A youtube channel : <a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/post/null" title="https://www.youtube.com/user/DesignCourse">Design Course</a></p>
<p>It is a very good youtube channel with amazing content. Every video is clear and concise. I like how everything is displayed and  explained. I started to watch a lot of its video today and I want to reproduce almost all of them. He makes a lot of design courses and dome design reviews. For everyone interested by webdesign and front end development, I recommend this channel! </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>TIL - TID</title>
        <author>
            <name>Marc</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://wagam.github.io/tild/til-tid.html"/>
        <id>https://wagam.github.io/tild/til-tid.html</id>

        <updated>2020-03-25T15:35:28+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    By this new blog, I want to share what I learn every day and what I discovered. Tht's why you will see two types of articles: TIL for Today I Learnt and TID for Today I Discovered. It has two functions: it &lt;ill help to remember&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>By this new blog, I want to share what I learn every day and what I discovered. Tht's why you will see two types of articles: TIL for Today I Learnt and TID for Today I Discovered. </p>
<p>It has two functions: it &lt;ill help to remember what I can learn everyday and it wan help some people to discover new things as I discover them too. </p>
<p> </p>
<p>Enjoy! </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
